A little bear goes a long way.
Paddington in Peru is a family, comedy, adventure
film directed by Dougal Wilson.
Paddington travels to Peru to visit his beloved Aunt Lucy,
who now resides at the Home for Retired Bears.
With the Brown Family in tow, a thrilling adventure ensues when a mystery plunges them into an
unexpected journey through the Amazon rainforest and up to the mountain peaks of Peru.
Paddington Brown (voice), played by Ben Whishaw.
Henry Brown, played by Hugh Bonneville.
Mary Brown, played by Emily Mortimer.
Jonathan Brown, played by Samuel Joslin.
Judy Brown, played by Madeleine Harris.
Hunter Cabot, played by Antonio Banderas.
Paddington in Peru is a 2024 American live-action animated adventure comedy film directed
by Dougal Wilson and written by Mark Burton, Jon Foster, and James Lamont.
It is the third installment in the Paddington film series, which
are based on the Paddington stories by Michael Bond.
The film stars Hugh Bonneville, Emily Mortimer, Julie Walters, Olivia Colman,
Antonio Banderas and Ben Whishaw as the voice of Paddington.
The film sees the Brown family travelling through the
Peruvian jungle to find Paddington's aunt Lucy.
The film entered development in February 2021, and the title
Paddington in Peru was announced in June 2022.
It is the feature film debut of Wilson.
Principal photography took place between July and October
2023, in the United Kingdom, Colombia and Peru.
Paddington in Peru was released in cinemas in the United Kingdom by StudioCanal on 8 November
2024 and in the United States by Sony Pictures Releasing on 14 Feburary 2025.
It grossed $192 million and received positive reviews from critics.
A fourth film is in development.
The film explores themes of rescue, sequel, bear, based on
children's book, aunt nephew relationship.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.